cricruns.com 2015-03-16

# Privacy Policy | Cricruns.com

### Privacy Policy 

cricruns.com is concerned and committed to preserve the privacy of the users. This privacy policy session explains about the privacy policy, information which cricruns.com collect from users and how it is used.

Please read the following privacy policy carefully before using the cricruns.com website.cricruns.com does not attempt to determine the identity of any cricruns.com user by analyzing web usage paths. 

### Information collected by Cricruns.com from users

You can view live scores, news, updates, images, videos, etc of cricket in cricruns.com without any registration or providing any personal details. However, cricruns.com gathers the following information when you use the site: the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) of the web page from which you visited cricruns.com, your Internet Protocol (IP) address which may include a domain name, server name, content type from the page headers. 

### For what purpose the information is used by Cricruns.com

cricruns.com gathers information from you only to provide you with a better service. It is collected only for internal records and to prepare reports based on figures. cricruns.com uses cookies for verifying that you are a cricruns.com user and it also uses for counting and tracking your number of visits to cricruns.com. In addition, it also uses cookies to determine the number of visitors that came to the cricruns.com website through a particular advertisement. Cricruns.com uses IP address to gather broad demographic information such as your general geographic location and Internet Service Provider, server type, content type etc. This demographic information may also be used by cricruns.com to analyze aggregate web usage behavior. 

### Security of your information in Cricruns.com

cricruns.com makes sure that the information of the users is protected from hackers and abusive users. It uses highly advanced computer security safeguards to protect its databases and servers against risks of loss, unauthorized access, destruction, misuse, modification, or inadvertent or improper disclosure of data. These risks, however, cannot be completely eliminated and cricruns.com therefore cannot guarantee complete security in exceptional situations. Cricruns.com segregates certain personally identifiable information provided by you. Restricted Access to the information:

The access to the above mentioned information gathered from the users? computer is restricted only to the admin of cricruns.com. The data are used only internally and stored in the cricruns.com database. cricruns.com does not provide the information to any third-party site or customers and hence the security of the details is ensured. 

### Links to other sites

cricruns.com website may have links to various other sites and cricruns.com is not responsible for the privacy and security of the personal information collected by those sites from you.

### Changes in the policy

Privacy policy is subjected to change periodically as the contents of the site get updated and new features are introduced dynamically. Though cricruns.com informs users about the changes, it is your responsibility too to check the policy frequently for the recent changes.
